// COPIED FROM: // https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1Z83KQDqBV3xBzS2sDMeLI_dSioZlWkmGaVx_WjfhfAU/edit?usp=sharing
let questions = 
[{
    question: "When is it OK to leave trailing spaces?",
    correctAnswer: [0, 2],
    answers: ["Never", "When it looks pretty", "Never", "When you're a rus"]
},
{
    question: "When do you stop being a rus?",
    correctAnswer: [0],
    answers: ["After AD", "After first year", "After AP", "Never"]
},
{
    question: "What is the 42th prime number?",
    correctAnswer: [2],
    answers: ["1337", "251", "181", "42"]
},
{
    question: "What makes a robot soft?",
    correctAnswer: [2],
    answers: ["Its feelings", "Your mom", "Its soft shell", "Erectile Disfunction"]
},
{
    question: "Which one is not a programming language?",
    correctAnswer: [1],
    answers: ["Brainfuck", "true", "Whitespace", "Piet"]
},
{
    question: "What is the best editor?",
    correctAnswer: [0],
    answers: ["Vim", "Atom", "Emacs", "Nano"]
},
{
    question: "What is the best base for array indexing?",
    correctAnswer: [1],
    answers: ["1", "0", "½", "π"]
},
{
    question: "Which of these typically have the most peak FLOPS?",
    correctAnswer: [3],
    answers: ["CPU", "GPU", "APU", "TPU"]
},
{
    question: "Which of the following have been the longest at DIKU?",
    correctAnswer: [2],
    answers: ["Pawel Winter", "Mads Nielsen", "Torben Mogensen", "Fritz Henglein"]
},
{
    question: "Which software license came first?",
    correctAnswer: [0],
    answers: ["GNU General Public License Version 2", "Do What The Fuck You Want To Public License Version 2",
        "2-Clause BSD License", "Apache License Version 2.0"]
},
{
    question: "Finish the sentence: 'From pwn import ?'",
    correctAnswer: [3],
    answers: ["root", "Club Mate", "the_gibson", "*"]
},
{
    question: "Which is the objectively best beer?",
    correctAnswer: [1],
    answers: ["Grøn Tuborg", "GT", "Limfjords porter", "Ale 16"]
}];